

Henrik Mjaaland

Computer Engineer

18 November 1993



Høgevollsveien 19B, 4315 Sandnes, Rogaland



+47 90215974



http://github.com/henmja



henrikmjaaland@hotmail.com

About Me ———

I am a computer engineer from Sandnes, Norway. I have a bachelor's degree in Computer Science, and I handed in my master's thesis this spring. For my master's thesis I wrote about fake news detection in social media using neural networks. The thesis is available on github: https://www.github.com/henmja.I have previously worked as a production operator, seller, gardener, and as a warehouse worker. Presently, I am working as a control technician for Nærbø Kyllingslakt. There, the tasks are IT-related (f.ex. control the assembly lines). As a person, I am social, hard-working and honest.

Skills ——— Python

Java

MATLAB

Go

Javascript

PHP

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Education

2017-2020 M.Sc. University of Stavanger

University of Stavanger

Sandnes VGS

Computer Science

2014-2016 B.Sc.

Computer Science

2009-2012 General Studies (Science)

Realfag

Portfolio

https://www.github.com/henmja

Website

https://www.henrikmjaaland.com

Certificates

2012 Driver's License, Class B 2012 Forklift License, T1 2016 **Boating License**

Experience

Current	Control Technician	Nærbø Kyllingslakt

2017-18 **Production Operator** Nortura Forus

2016 Gardener Facility Services

2015 Warehouse Worker Megaflis Forus

2013-14 Seller Burger Pizza Companiet

2012 Warehouse Worker REMA 1000 Distribusjon

References

References are given on demand.